visitsealife.com 2017-03-02

# Privacy Policy - Official SEA LIFE Website

## Privacy Policy

This web site is owned and run by Merlin Entertainments (SEA LIFE) Ltd as agent for and on behalf of Merlin Attractions Operations Limited. SEA LIFE recognises that your privacy is important, and is committed to preserving it. This policy sets out our policy in relation to any personal information which you supply to us through your use of this website...

Booking your SEA LIFE tickets online is quick, easy, convenient and safe.

SEA LIFE makes every effort to maintain customer confidentiality when securing an online payment. This includes ensuring the security of your credit card details and other personal information. All of your personal information is encrypted as it travels over the Internet.  

**How we collect data, and what we do with it**

You are in control of what information we collect about you. By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. However, if you choose not to share your information some areas of the web site may not be accessible or useable. We may ask you for information about yourself when you purchase tickets or other products or services, when you enter competitions or register for promotions or when you request brochures or other information. We may also invite you to complete surveys or provide us with feedback. We and our appointed advertising company also collect anonymous information about your use of the web site from cookies and by the use of pixel tags. We may match information gathered from these sources with any information you have given us about yourself for the purposes explained in this policy.

**Administration and non-marketing use disclosure**

We will use the information you enter at the site for administration purposes and any other purposes made clear in the data entry forms themselves, in any relevant terms or conditions and on any pages or emails which link to such forms. We may conduct analysis of user traffic. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

1\. in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets

2\. if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of The Merlin Entertainments Group, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purpose of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Direct Marketing**

If you book a ticket from us, the data you give us about yourself, will enable us to give you updates other than through our web site, using the contact details you provide, on promotions and services we think may interest you or to involve you in market research. To improve our picture of your interests we may link the data you give us with any data we have gathered (via cookies) about your use of the site. In some cases we may also wish to share your data with other parts of the Tussauds group or third party entities that process personal information on our behalf so that they can update you on promotions and services they think may be of interest to you.

Whenever we ask you for information about yourself, if you have indicated that you wish to receive direct marketing material from us and/or from third parties, your personal details will be included in a database compiled for direct marketing purposes and from time to time, you may receive these marketing communications. This will enable us to keep you informed about offers and events run by various attractions across the Merlin Entertainments Group, including Alton Towers Resort, THORPE PARK, Warwick Castle, Madame Tussauds, The EDF Energy London Eye and SEA LIFE.

If you have indicated that you wish to receive direct marketing material or e-mail updates from us, and/or from third parties but subsequently change your mind, you should notify us at merlin@acxiom.com. As soon after this as is reasonably practicable, we will remove your name from the relevant database. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your data is used by third parties in accordance with this policy.

**Links to other websites**

We use links to improve your experience of our web site. We will always seek to make these links clear, so that you know you have left our web site. However, please be aware that these web sites are owned and run by other companies and organisations and we cannot accept responsibility for any information you choose to divulge to a linked web site. Such websites have their own privacy policies and please check these policies before you submit personal data to them.

**Statistical Data**

We try to ensure that our web site offers visitors exactly what they are looking for - to help us achieve this goal we may analyse anonymous data collected by cookies about how visitors use the web site. Such data also helps us to measure the success of our advertising campaigns. We may also collect Internet Protocol addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and for system administration, but we don't link these addresses to any person's name or identity.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small amounts of information, which we store on your computer. Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies although in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site. To disable cookies consult your browsers help files and follow the steps shown.

**Security and Data Retention**

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

**Accessing and updating**

You are entitled to see a copy of any personal data (as defined in the Data Protection Act 1998) held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. We are entitled by law to charge a small fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**Contact**

Any comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your data are welcomed and should be emailed to us at deborah.luckham@merlinentertainments.biz.

or addressed to us at:

Merlin Entertainments (SEA LIFE) Ltd

3 market close

Poole

Dorset

BH15 1NQ 

**Changes to this policy**

Because we are constantly improving our sites there may be developments in how we use your data - all such developments will be promptly notified to you in this policy and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.
